我不是人
我不是东西
我错了我有罪
对不起我错了
我该死我错了
你们八大组忘恩负义
通敌叛国
狼心狗肺天地不容
接下来我会将你们送到大厦军法司
让你们接受法律的制裁
你们祖辈所创下的基业
也将在你们手里毁于一旦
主席
周旋我错了
我知道我错了
我格格也是一时糊涂
我求求你你再给我一次机会好不好
我求求你了
周旋我也错了
我没有判过的意思
求你不要灭我冤家
哎呀周杰
我愿意为你做牛做马
不做小妾都行
求你放我一马
我绝对我们错了
不困了鳄鱼的眼泪
永远不值得同情
来人将他们打入天牢
只要我周旋一日还在打下
就永不会灭
射门威武
周全
这次如果没有你
还不知道整个大厦
会落到怎样飞滩
那你愿意
与我一起登顶世界
看尽山河繁华吗
荣幸之际
I am not human
I am not a thing
I was wrong. I'm guilty.
Sorry, I was wrong.
Damn it, I was wrong.
You eight groups are ungrateful
Collaboration and treason
Wolves and dogs cannot tolerate heaven and earth
Next I will send you to the Military Justice Division of the Building
Let you be punished by the law
The legacy of your ancestors
It will also be destroyed at your hands
Chairperson
I was wrong.
I know I was wrong.
I was also confused for a while
I beg you, can you give me another chance?
I beg you.
I was wrong too
I didn't mean to judge it.
Please don't destroy my enemy
Oops Zhou Jie
I am willing to be a cow and a horse for you.
Don't be a concubine
Please let me go
I'm sure we were wrong.
Not sleepy crocodile tears
Never worthy of sympathy
Somebody throw them in jail.
As long as I'm still laying
Will never die
Shoot mighty
comprehensive
This time without you
I don't know the whole building yet
How will it land?
Then would you like to
Come with me to the top of the world
Do you see all the bustling mountains and rivers?
honored occasion